Register to The Lowell Mason Papers
Yale University Music Library
- William Mason, Series VIII
  - Miscellaneous Items, VIII.D
    For a portrait of William Mason in the Music Library Collection see: Lb50/Zga/2.
    - Pamphlet and fragment of pamphlet, no date (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Old Catalog Cards and Librarian's Notes Concerning the Lowell Mason Collection., Series IX
  - Contains old catalog cards and notes re the Lowell Mason Collection by Eva Judd O'Meara. (Box 15)